Mmm.
Hey.
Hi.
You have to got to try
this cheesecake.
Oh, you know
I'm not that much
of a sweet tooth.
( mumbling )
Oh, my God, it's so creamy.
Oh, my God
that is the best cheesecake
I've ever had.
Where did you get this?
It was at the front door
when I got home.
Somebody sent it to us.
Chandler, this is not
addressed to you.
This is addressed
to Mrs. Braverman downstairs.
( gasps )
Thief.
I... I didn't read the
box before I opened it
and you can't
return a box
after you've
opened the box.
Why not?
Because it's too delicious.
Chandler, you stole
this cheesecake.
That is wrong.
No, no, no,
it is going to be okay
because Mrs. Braverman is going
to send away for a free one
and that way we all win.
The only losers are the big
cheesecake conglomerate...
"Mama's Little Bakery."
I feel terrible.
I'm a horrible, horrible,
horrible person.
Mmm... I'm sorry, what?
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's DOA ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
All right,
I should get going.
Big day at work.
You know I'm in coma?
Well, today
they do this test on me
and turns out
I'm not brain-dead.
So...
Ah, ah, ah, Mr. Smarty-Pants
it's just my character
that's not brain-dead.
So, Pheebs,
we still on for tonight?
Absolutely.
All right, I'll
see you at 8:00.
Okay.
Oh, what's at 8:00?
Oh, I have dinner plans
with Joey.
We get together
about once a month
to discuss the rest of you guys.
Wow, did not know that.
May I say how lovely
you look today?
Duly noted.
Oh, so for tomorrow
do you want
to rent a car
and drive down
together, or what?
What are you
talking about?
Cousin Frannie's wedding;
it's tomorrow night.
You were invited?
No.
Oh, my God,
I can't believe this.
I knew that
mom and dad were invited
but I thought that was it.
I mean, from the ages
of seven to nine
Frannie and I
were inseparable.
Well, maybe since
the age of nine
Frannie's made some new friends.
Well... it's probably
just a mistake.
Let me call
Aunt Cheryl, okay?
Maybe you are invited
and the invitation just
got lost in the mail.
Yeah... you call her
and tell her that
you know,
when we were kids
her precious little Frannie
tried to undress me
several times, okay?
And if I
hadn't have stopped her
there probably wouldn't
even be a wedding to go to.
She tried to
undress me, too.
I used to undress
my cousin Glenn.
( chuckles )
Joseph Francis Tribbiani
are you home yet?
Um, I think
he's still out.
What's wrong?
Well, I'll tell you,
Rachel Karen Green.
I had plans
with Joey tonight
and he left me this note.
"Pheebs, can't make it.
"Got a date.
Talk to you later.
Big Daddy."
Big Daddy?
Oh, that's a nickname
we were trying out.
Hey, you know what nickname
never caught on?
"The Ross-a-tron."
Hey.
Oh, here's Joseph Francis.
Hey, way... oh...
What are you middle
naming me for?
I left you a note.
So, what? That doesn't give you
the right to ditch me.
Hey, you can cancel
plans with friends
if there's a possibility
for sex.
Phoebe, he's right.
That is the rule.
I don't accept this rule.
When we make plans,
I expect you show up.
Okay? I can't just
be a way to kill time
till you meet
someone better.
You know, boyfriends
and girlfriends
are going to come and go,
but this is for life.
Wow... I'm so sorry.
I had no idea
it would bother you this much.
Well, it does.
Okay, can I make it up
to you, huh?
I'm sorry.
How about dinner tomorrow night?
I'll pay for myself.
Okay, you wore me down.
Hey, Joe,
while you're over there
how about another beer
for "The Ross-a-tron."
The Ross... is that back?
Hi.
The other cheesecake came.
They delivered it
to the wrong address again.
So, just bring it back
downstairs.
What's the problem?
I can't seem to say good-bye.
Are you serious?
Chandler, we ate an entire
cheesecake two days ago
and you want more?
Well, I've forgotten
what it tastes like, okay?
It was cheesecake.
It was fine.
It had a buttery, crumbly,
graham cracker crust
with a very... rich
yet light...
cream cheese filling.
Well, my whole mouth
just filled with saliva.
Okay, you know what?
Forget it.
We are just hungry.
We have not had lunch.
We are just light-headed.
So, let us go out
and have lunch
and forget
about the cheesecake.
Yeah, we'll drop it off
downstairs
so we're not tempted.
Good idea. Where do you
want to go to lunch?
Mama's Little Bakery,
Chicago, Illinois.
Oh... Mel Torme died.
Joey, that paper's,
like, a year old.
Oh, does that mean
the Sam Goody sale is over?
Hey.
So, I finally heard
back from Aunt Cheryl
and apparently
it wasn't a mistake.
Uh, there's-there's
limited seating in the hall...
Limited seating?
I am just one
tiny person.
Well, yeah,
but she doesn't know that.
I mean, the last
time she saw you
you would have turned
one of those little
wedding chairs
into kindling.
Uh... "limited seating."
Oh, that is such
a lame excuse.
That's not the reason
why she's not inviting me.
What's the big deal?
I wasn't even invited
to the ceremony
just the reception,
and you know what?
If it makes you
feel any better
Joan and I will just
make an appearance
and then, and then
we'll-we'll leave
early as a sign
of protest.
Joan?
Yeah, Joan Tedeschi.
My date.
She's an assistant
professor
in the linguistics
department.
Tall, very beautiful
and despite what
some people say
not broad-backed.
Wait a minute.
You got
"Ross Geller and guest"?
I wasn't invited,
and you got "and guest"?
Uh, excuse me...
I do have to interrupt
on Ross's behalf.
I think the rule applies here.
Since he has a chance
to get on broad-back...
Not broad-back!
MONICA:
Wait a minute.
You're bringing me.
Well, I can't
cancel on Joan.
Why not?
Because-- did
you not hear me?--
she's an assistant
professor
in the linguistics
department, okay?
They're wild.
Why do you want
to come anyway?
Because...
she's my cousin.
I mean,
we grew up together.
We're family, you know
and that's...
that's important to me.
Okay, all right,
I'll take you.
I'll go call Joan.
Oh, that's nice.
Family should
be there, huh?
This is her wedding;
happiest day of her life.
We'll see.
( Chandler sighs )
Well, thank you for lunch.
Wait a minute. I didn't pay.
I thought you paid.
So, apparently we just don't pay
for food anymore.
( chuckles )
Do you see what I see?
( gasps )
It's still there.
Mrs. Braverman must be out.
She could be
out of town.
Maybe she'll be
gone for months.
By then, the cheesecake
may have gone bad.
We don't want
her to come back
to bad cheesecake.
No, that could kill her.
Well, we don't want that.
No, so we're
protecting her.
We should take it.
We should move quick.
Why?
Because I think
I just heard her
moving around in there.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
( gasps )
Oh, my God, that's David.
David who?
PHOEBE:
David, the
scientist guy.
David that I
was in love with.
David who went to Russia
and broke my heart David.
Oh, my God.
You say someone's name enough
they turn around.
Phoebe.
David.
What's... what are
you doing here?
Aren't you supposed
to be in Russia?
Yeah, I'm just in town
for a conference.
Oh.
Um, God...
You look phenomenal.
Well... yeah.
You look great, too.
Did you get a haircut?
Yeah, well,
I-I-I got, like, 30 of them.
Yeah.
Um, look, I-I-I got
a confession to make.
Uh-huh.
I-I was hoping
to run into you here.
I didn't know whether
I should call or not.
I was only in town
for a few days
and, you know, I didn't
want to intrude on your life
or anything like that
but I really
wanted to see you
but I didn't know
if you wanted to see me.
Well... of course I
would want to see you.
I... I think about
you all the time.
Really?
Because I think about you
all the time.
Really?
There's a statue in Minsk
that reminds me of you so much.
I mean, um,
it's actually of Lenin
but-but, you know...
Yeah.
at certain angles...
Um... anyway
do you want
to have dinner tonight?
Yes.
Oh, no.
Oh, uh, what?
I can't.
I can't believe I have plans.
Can you do it
tomorrow night, though?
Uh, no, I have to go
in a few hours.
I have to be on the red-eye.
Well, listen, you know,
next time you're in Minsk, um...
Phoebe, can I talk
to you for a second?
Uh-huh.
What are you doing?
Well, I have plans
with Joey tonight.
So? He'll understand.
No, he won't,
and that's not even the point.
Monica, I made a whole speech
about how you do not
cancel plans with friends
and now,
you know, what?
Just because potentially
the love of my life
comes back from Russia
just for one night
I should change my beliefs?
I should change my beliefs.
No.
No, no. If I don't have
my principles
I don't have anything.
God, you are so strong.
Or, I should rush through dinner
with Joey
and I can meet David at 9:00.
Oh, my God,
that is so good.
I'm full.
And yet I know,
if I stop eating this
I'll regret it.
Hey.
Hey, what have
you got there?
Oh, it's, um...
It's tofu cake.
Do you want some?
( groans )
( sighs )
What are you
doing tonight?
Huh?
Dude, dude.
Oh!
Sorry.
Uh, I got those plans
with Phoebe. Why?
Oh, really?
Monica said she
had a date at 9:00.
What? Tonight?
That's what Monica said.
After she gave me
that big speech
she goes and makes
a date with a guy
on the same night
she has plans with me?
I think she's trying to pull
a fast one on Big Daddy.
Oh, here--
I think this is us.
Limited seating, my ass.
Let's just see
who made the cut.
Hi.
I'm Monica Geller.
How do you know
the bride and groom?
Oh, I used to work with Frannie.
Used to work with her.
Used to.
I'm a relative
and I didn't get invited.
A blood relative.
Blood.
Stop saying blood
to strangers.
So, how about
you, hmm?
How do you know
the happy couple?
We went to college with
both of them,
and now we live next door.
Okay, you're fine.
Hey.
Are you guys ready?
Yes, I will have
a green salad
house dressing,
and water's fine.
Okay.
And for you, sir.
Yeah--
this slow-roasted salmon.
Just how slow are we talking?
It's already been roasted.
Oh, then no.
Maybe I should hear
those specials again.
Oh, Joey, we've
heard the specials
three times, okay?
There's prime rib,
mahi-mahi
and a very special
lobster ravioli.
Actually, we're
out of the lobster ravioli.
Oh, well, that
changes everything.
You know what, Pheebs?
Huh?
You were right before.
Mm-hmm.
Friends are
so important.
Yeah, I'm very
wise, I know.
You know what
I really want?
What?
Is to have a long, long talk.
You know, get Joey
out on the open road
and really open him up.
Any progress?
Yes.
I will have
the lobster ravioli.
Oh, my God, Joey.
This is taking forever.
What's the rush, what?
( stuttering ):
Well, I just...
I have, you know,
I have an appointment
and it's very important.
Oh, well, what is it?
Well...
It's a date.
A date?
No, no, Pheebs.
You must be mistaken
because I know you
wouldn't schedule a date
on the same night you
have plans with a friend.
Come on, Joey, don't make
me feel badly about this.
No, I'm gonna.
That's right, yeah.
You made me feel
really guilty
about going out
with that girl
like I did something
terrible to you.
Now, Pheebs, you're
doing the same thing.
It's not the same thing.
This is totally different.
This is with David.
Remember David?
The scientist guy?
He's very special to me.
Okay, well, my girl from
the other night was special.
She was a scientist, too.
She was?
Well, she graduated high school.
Okay, whatever.
You know what?
I don't have time
to convince you
because he's only
here for four hours
and I'm going
to go see him.
Fine!
Yeah.
What are you
still doing here?
I told you,
lobster ravioli!
Hey.
Hey, I was just
about to leave.
I didn't think
you were coming.
Oh, I wouldn't
have missed this.
Well, I'm very
glad you're here.
Oh, you're
such a gentleman.
Come on, we're
going to my place.
Mmm.
Are you eating
the cheesecake without me?
Uh-uh.
I will give you $100
to whistle right now.
How could you eat
the cheesecake without me?
Oh, what are
you going to do?
You going to go run
and tell Monica?
Are you going
to tell Joey?
No, because you'd have
to tell them what we did.
We are dessert stealers.
We are living
outside of the law.
You know what?
I don't trust you
with this cake anymore.
And I got it first.
And I'm taking it back.
What?
No, no, no, you don't.
Oh, yes!
You think I
trust you with it?
No, we're going to split it.
You take half and I take half.
That's not fair.
You've already had some.
Oh, then, you know what?
I think Monica would be
very interested to know
that you called
her cheesecake dry and mealy.
What do we use to split it?
Okay.
All right, pick a half.
Well, this side looks bigger.
Mm-hmm.
But there's more crust
on this side.
You know?
So, maybe if I measured...
For God's sake,
just pick a piece!
I pick that one.
Ha, so the smaller piece.
Okay.
There you go.
Enjoy your half, my friend.
But that is it.
No sharing, no switching
and don't come crying to me
if you eat your piece too fast.
( screams )
Oh...
Oh!
All right, you got to give me
some of your piece.
Oh, no, no.
No switching, no sharing,
and don't come crying to me!
Ha, ha, ha.
I may just sit here
and have my cake all day.
Just sit here in
the hallway and eat my...
Ross, sweetheart!
Oh, hey, Aunt Millie.
Isn't it a beautiful wedding?
Yes, yes it is.
Every time on the lips.
Why, why on the lips?
( applause )
There's Frannie.
Won't she be happy to see me?
Now, wait a minute.
You be nice, all right?
I didn't bring you here
so you could ambush her.
Frannie was the one
who found your Playboys
and showed them to Mom.
That bitch.
Monica!
What...
Am I doing here?
Why? Surprised to see me?
Ross brought me.
How do you like that?
Hi, Frannie,
congratulations.
You invite my brother
you invite my whole
family and not me?
Why?
Why wouldn't you want
me at your wedding?
What could I
have possibly done?
Stuart.
I believe you
know my husband.
So it's really
a question of
who could you
have possibly done?
Oh, I hate this,
but I have to go.
I can't miss my flight.
Are you sure?
I bet there's another
flight to Minsk in...
July.
( speaking Russian )
That's really beautiful.
What does it mean?
Please clean my beakers.
I don't get out
of the lab much.
( giggles )
I thought it meant...
something else.
Yeah, I, well,
I really, actually
wanted to say, um, that.
But I figured
I probably shouldn't
because, you know
I have to leave.
No, you're right,
you're right.
Don't say it.
I do, though.
I do, too.
Bye, Phoebe.
Bye.
Okay, now's not the time,
Joey, all right?
You can yell at me tomorrow.
No, no, no, Pheebs.
I'm not going to yell at you.
I just, you know, started
thinking about you and David
and I remember how bummed you
were the first time he left.
I just...
Oh, Pheebs, come here.
Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay.
The only guy I've
ever been crazy about
is going to Minsk and I
may never see him again.
Hey, you know,
you could always visit him.
Oh, right--
like they're
going to let me
have a passport.
Is there anything I can do?
Whatever you need.
Well, but now
if you could achieve
positronic distillation
of subatomic particles,
you know
before he does, then
he could come back.
I could give it a shot.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Oh, yay, look.
There's a piece that
doesn't have floor on it.
Stick to your side.
Come on, now.
All right,
what are we having?
Oh, wait.
I forgot my wrap.
Okay, wait here.
Hi, sweetie!
Are you leaving?
Well...
Give us a kiss.
Come on.
( groans )
Why?!
Why on the lips?!